All members of this group reviewed all the code being submitted and have a good understanding of it. All members of this group declare that no code other than their own has been submitted. We both acknowledge that not understanding our own work will result in a zero on this assignment, and that if the code is detected to be plagiarised, severe academic penalties will be applied when the case is brought forward to the Dean of Arts and Science.